

Nikos Roumeliotis

Security Engineer/Penetration Tester

+(31) 063 3910 251 - nikos.roume@icloud.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikos-roumeliotis/

SKILLS

Javascript/Node.js/Typescript
PHP/Laravel/Wordpress
Python/Flask/Django
Software Design/Architecture
Web Application Pentesting/Code reviews
Problem solving/Debugging
Written and verbal communication

ABOUT ME

Security&Software Engineer with 5+ years of experience mostly on web applications. Self-motivated, quick-learner, security-minded, always looking forward to new technologies improving my skills. In addition to software development, I have learned many web frameworks using PHP, Javascript/Typescript, Python, MySQL/NoSQL. Out of work I like to do CTF's and watch movies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ethical Hacker (4/2021 - Present)

Eurofins Cyber Security, The Netherlands (Full-time)

- Penetration Testing (Web Application)
- Penetration Testing (Infrastructure)
- Security Research

Full Stack Developer (8/2020 - 1/2021)

Experiencegift, The Netherlands (Full-time)

- Frontend / Wordpress, HTML, CSS/CSS3, Javascript
- Penetration Testing (Applications Security)

Security & Software Engineer (8/2018 - 8/2020)

Onyx Cybersecurity, The Netherlands (Full-time)

- Angular/Typescript/Node.js/Unit Tests
- Wordpress/Themes/Plugins
- · Laravel Flask Docker
- Penetration Testing (Web Applications/Infrastructure Networks)

LANGUAGES

English

Greek (Native)

CERTIFICATIONS









WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer (2015 - 2018)

iSight, Greece (Full-time)

- Wordpress, HTML, CSS/CSS3, Javascript
- Laravel
- MySQL
- Penetration Testing (Web Applications/Infrastructure Networks)

Freelacer Web Developer (2012 - 2015)

• PHP, Wordpress, Joomla, Drupal, Javascript, HTML, CSS

EDUCATION

Technical Lyceum

· Computing Accounting and Finance

Intergraphics Studies

- Accounting Applications | SingularLogic
- Computing with Accounting and Finance